[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Diego] The Ardientes were after me.
No one else should've gotten involved.
I'll go face them
so no one else gets hurt.
[Anna] Don't blame yourself.
What the Ardientes did was not your fault!
Don't go, Diego. The people here need you.
I know you can't wait to go
after the Ardientes.
The same goes for me, Jepoy!
But we need to stick to the plan.
Julio won't know what hit him.
[Diego] Divine Uytengco?
[Arthur] Ivy asked me to bring
her here. But she won't talk.
You're better at this.
She might listen to you.
Jaguar was the one who tried
to kill your son.
You betrayed me!
[Raul] That's the gun I gave Madrigal.
He probably did that for personal reasons.
Then kill Madrigal!
[Julio] Colonel Sanggano here
just informed me
that they already know
where to find Madrigal.
Let's go make that bastard suffer.
What's the problem?
If this is the way my own group
and boss are going to treat me,
then I'll just leave.
Give me Madrigal, or else,
I will book you a one-way ticket to hell
with Satan as your bodyguard.
-[Jepoy] I'm leaving this place.
-[Ivy] Where are you going?
Somewhere far away.
So I can protect you all.
I'll return to the shadows.
[Emilia sighs]
It makes me wonder why up to now,
we still haven't caught
the person who shot Arnaldo.
I'm thinking that person
might just be around us, Papa.
Who knows? You were probably
with them yesterday.
[ominous music playing]
Emilia, if you're alluding to Miss Aguas,
she has cleared herself…
for now.
So, stop picking on her.
Papa, aren't you wondering why
she doesn't want you and Jaguar
to face each other?
What if she's in cahoots with Jaguar?
Plus Diego and Madrigal?
[ominous music playing]
You have an overactive imagination.
You know, just to satisfy you
because you're so annoying,
and since you hate her that much,
why don't you keep an eye on Miss Aguas?
So, you'll do something.
What? Me? [laughs] No way.
You've gotta be kidding me,
Papa. I don't want to.
Why?
Are you scared of her?
Me?
Scared of Ivy? Papa, have you forgotten?
I'm a lioness.
She's nothing but a pesky rat!
So why would I be scared of her?
Do you think she's capable
of beating me? Never.
We'll see.
Hey! It's so hot in here!
Let me go! Get me out of this place!
I still have a…
…business to run!
And my children, they need me!
Just let me go! Come on!
[Divine grunting, panting]
These are your kids, right?
Stephanie, Macie, and your youngest?
[tense music playing]
Ever since your husband died…
…they could only depend on you.
And now, what do you think
would happen to them
if you were to die as well?
Where did you get that?!
Leave my children out of this!
I'm not that easy to put down, okay?
Even if you kill me,
which I doubt you can do,
Emilia will take care of my children.
You're quite dumb, Divine.
Do you really think Emilia will help you?
[Diego] What if I tell you…
…that Emilia won't help you?
Impossible. Emilia owes me a lot!
[Divine] Huh?!
Good point.
You only deposited millions
of pesos to your bank account
just to give it to her. Am I right?
[tense music playing]
We have a copy of all
your bank transactions.
Aren't you ashamed?
You stole the people's money.
Don't you feel guilty?
Why would I be?!
This whole town's money
isn't enough to pay
for everything Emilia Ardiente owes me!
[tense music playing]
You won't get anything from me!
So, let me go!
Let me go and leave
my children out of this!
Well, Arthur? What should we do
with these three?
If you hurt my children,
I'll make sure you'll pay!
If you do something to my children,
I'll make sure your whole family pays!
Take a look at this.
Divine Uytengco's husband reportedly died
of a heart attack.
But he was healthy and had
no history of any illnesses.
That's why I was wondering…
what really happened
to Divine Uytengco's husband.
He may have suffered
the same fate as my father.
[Camia] Get out of here!
You killed my husband!
I have a strong hunch Emilia
is also responsible…
for the death of Divine's husband.
I don't understand.
Why would she defend Emilia?
If… If I mention this to Mrs.
Uytengco, she might speak up.
No, Diego. I have something else in mind.
In case you haven't noticed,
if you observe Divine carefully,
she's all about money.
She'll drop you for the next
big buck in a heartbeat.
So, I'm going to gain
Divine Uytengco's trust.
Gain her trust? By bribing her?
I'll buy her off or do whatever it takes
to get her on our side.
Make sure it's nice, okay? Okay, good.
Excuse me. Good afternoon.
Oh, hello. Um, how may I help you?
I'm looking for your most expensive piece.
Okay. Right here.
[tense music playing]
These three?
Yes, but the middle one
is the most expensive.
And, I think it's perfect for you.
[upbeat music playing]
It's really shiny.
And now this too.
Divine and I had an agreement.
It's been ages,
and she still hasn't
kept her part of the deal.
Oh! It's as if you don't know her!
Remember Barcelona last year?
Didn't she go out
with the bartender there?
That's why I came here
to see her daughter.
I'm sure Stephanie knows where her mom is.
Stephanie!
-Hi, Mrs. Emilia!
-Hi.
Where's your Mom?
[tense music playing]
Ivy!
Emilia.
Small world.
What do the millennials call it?
I'm "shookt" to see you.
Well, you can't blame me,
seeing you here in my territory.
And mind you, huh?
In my friend's jewelry shop no less.
You know? I'm really starting
to feel like you're stalking me.
Emilia, what do people do
in a jewelry store?
Buy jewelry, right?
Unless you have a different
definition for this store.
I do. Maybe, um… A boxing ring?
War zone? Or hell? Choose one.
I think it's hell.
You'd feel right at home!
[tense music playing]
It was nice front-stabbing
with you, Emilia.
Excuse me. I'll just spend some money.
Miss?
Is this your most expensive piece?
Huh?
Cheap taste.
[tense music playing]
Where is this place?!
I told you to let me go!
[tense music playing]
Oh.
This is the most expensive
jewelry in my shop!
Did you buy it? Why?
Wasn't this given by your husband?
Listen.
I'll give this back to you
if you cooperate with us.
What do you want to know?
I was the one who bought that.
[dramatic music]
And the one who had you brought here.
Ivy Aguas?
Yes. Oh, yes.
That's right.
Your husband died
of a heart attack, right?
He had a heart attack…
but I heard your husband
was quite healthy.
He didn't even have any ailments.
Makes me wonder if he was yet
another victim of the Ardientes.
[somber music playing]
You think, Divine, that your
husband died of natural causes?
Or are you a victim of the Ardientes too?
[Divine sobbing]
I don't know. I don't know.
Truth is, my husband was a businessman.
-And I was an accountant.
-I know.
And Emilia knew I was envious of her life.
And then she told me
I could have her life.
I could live like a queen.
And then she offered me a proposition.
[tense music playing]
[stuttering] She told me to
transfer billions
of pesos of government funds
to my account.
And live like a queen.
[Divine crying]
My husband and I fought over it.
And then he threatened to expose Emilia.
That's it. That's why Emilia
had your husband killed.
Right? That's what happened, right?
Emilia had your husband killed, Divine.
It's all my fault! It's my fault!
I gave in. I helped her steal money.
I turned a blind eye and pretended
that I didn't see a thing!
What kind of a person am I?
I wasn't like that!
What kind of wife was I?
I allowed all this to happen.
But… What could I do?
I was pushed to a corner.
I was left with no choice.
How can I fight Emilia?
You can fight her.
Because she's just Emilia.
And I am Ivy Aguas.
[tense music playing]
If you agree to my plans,
Divine, if you say yes…
we'll work together,
and we'll bring Emilia down.
[Divine crying]
I promise you, Divine. I will help you.
I'll give you everything.
What about my kids?
We'll protect you.
We'll take care of you and your kids.
I'll protect you. Just trust me, Divine.
[tense music playing]
Aunt Claire, I haven't heard
anything from Divine,
and I'm getting worried.
I'm sure she's okay.
Why don't you call her daughters?
I already did, Auntie, and they
don't know where Divine is.
You know, I just wish she just
got into an accident or maybe,
she was found dead on a sidewalk.
Emilia.
Divine knows a lot
of my secrets, Aunt Claire.
And guess what? I just saw
Ivy Aguas at Divine's shop.
I have a feeling, Aunt Claire,
that someone is going to
use her against me,
and that's Ivy Aguas.
[Georgina] Regarding the criminal case
we filed against Arnaldo,
it will get delayed
because he's in a coma.
Well, Attorney, we should
just file a plunder case
against Emilia first.
It would be harder for Julio Ardiente
to run for office if we expose
Emilia's corrupt deeds.
We'll prepare the evidence
and testimony of Mrs. Uytengco.
We are going to file the case
as soon as possible.
And, Divine, you will be under
witness protective custody.
Thank you, Attorney.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
Divine. I promise you.
We'll help each other.
We'll take care of you.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Divine] Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
You know, I really don't wanna hear
about your incompetence, okay?
Just call me once you find Divine.
Understand? Okay?
-[maid] Ma'am! Ma'am!
-Oh, come on!
How many times do I have to
tell you not to bother me if--
-Ma'am.
-What's that?
Read the card.
"My big, bad, naughty girl, Emilia.
I miss your kiss and your big lips--"
That's enough. Give me that.
Get out! Leave!
[ominous music playing]
[giggling]
Emilia, what's that?
[ominous music playing]
Who sent that?
Well, you don't have the right to know.
I'm asking you. Who sent that?
It's from Jaguar.
[Raul] It's from Damian?
[phone ringing]
-I'll take these. Stop that!
-Hey! That's mine.
That's mine, Raul. You don't have--
Wait!
[phone ringing]
-Hey!
-Hello!
Did you like it?
You won't quit it, will you?
I was hoping to talk to Emilia, but fine…
Since you said you won't return…
my mask, and it also seems like
you don't want to return my men,
and my weapons…
maybe you could lend me your wife?
[laughs mockingly]
You bastard! Leave my wife out of this!
If I see you, you're going to get it!
I'm just getting started.
If you don't give back my mask…
you'll feel just how sharp
the Jaguar's fangs are.
I'll take back everything from you…
and even more, Raul.
I'll cut your fake fangs with a saw.
You bastard! Face me man-to-man!
Leave my wife out of this!
-[Damian] Just wait for it.
-Give it--
-Hello!
-[singsongs] Just wait for it.
[laughs mockingly]
Hello!
Tomas, keep an eye on Raul's group.
Find out if they're planning something.
And just like what I did to Emilia…
I will also sabotage their plans.
Is that clear?
Yes, boss.
[tense music playing]
Then why are you still
standing there?! Move!
[tense music playing]
Give that to me, Raul. That's enough.
You don't have the right
to touch my things!
You're not thinking straight, Emilia!
Huh!?
If that really was from Jaguar,
he wouldn't have
given you a phone.
He already gave you one, right?
Well, he told me his men are
on red alert, that's why I know.
[tense music playing]
There's an impostor?
I remember now. Jenny! Jenny!
-Ma'am?
-Throw these out.
Hurry! Get them out of the house!
Raul. Thank you for warning me.
But… how did you know?
Be more careful next time.
[tense music playing]
[man] This guy is wanted. Be careful.
Take a good look at the photo.
-[man] If you see him…
-[woman] Look. One million.
-[man] Sir…
-I could use a million pesos.
Yes, same.
--Post it, so everyone can see.
-I wish we would see him.
[man] Here. Here. Put it here.
Oh, I don't have a phone with me.
[man] This guy is wanted, ma'am.
If you see him, inform us right away.
There's a one-million-peso reward.
[woman] I think this guy's famous.
It's one million pesos if we find him.
I know. What crime did he commit?
Why's the reward so big?
I think he did something really bad.
Hey! Why are you taking that down?
This isn't real. This guy's dead.
-It looks like him.
-Yeah.
That's him!
Ah, hello. Hello, sir? Ah, yes.
We saw the man in the poster.
He's here in Sitio Otso. Yes. Sir. Hurry.
Damian keeps watching my every move.
If I push through with the mission,
I'm as good as dead.
Are you serious about that?
[laughs]
You're too dramatic.
You know, just push through
with the mission.
That way, Damian won't beat you to it.
Because if he does,
he'll get all the money,
which was meant for you.
And we wouldn't want that.
That's why you need
to push through with it.
But I'll have a hard time
because I don't have enough men.
Well, then force Madrigal
to work for you again.
[tense music playing]
Natalie, he shot my son.
I won't allow him to set foot
in this place again.
[scoffs] You're so dramatic. I love it.
Get over it.
Just kill him after the mission.
Right?
[tense music playing]
-Thank you.
-Okay. Thank you.
Jepoy.
Anna?
What are you doing here?
Are you following me?
Lily and Diego managed to make
the whistleblower confess.
We prepared a little something
at the hospital,
so we can tell Auntie Camia the good news.
Come with me.
I can't. Someone might follow us.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Boss, I found Madrigal.
You know what to do.
Watch him closely. We're on our way.
Yes, boss.
[sinister music playing]
Send them my regards.
All right, you need to go
before someone sees us.
-Jepoy.
-Anna, don't be stubborn.
If the Ardientes catch me,
I'm going down alone.
I can do this. Trust me.
Get going. Go on. Leave.
[tense music playing]
-[man] Got you!
-Here! Here!
Let go of me!
-Don't resist!
-Come with us!
-Anna!
-Let go of me!
-Stop! Jepoy! Stop it! Jepoy!
Jepoy!
-Stop it! Stop, or I'll shoot!
-[Jepoy] No! No! No!
Just take me.
-Jepoy.
-Don't! Just take me!
Take me instead!
Jepoy. Jepoy! Let go of me!
Tell that bastard to get up.
-Get up! Get up!
-[Anna yelping]
[Anna] Let go of me!
[panting] Anna…
-[Julio] Hey!
-[Anna] Jepoy!
-[Julio grunts]
-[Jepoy groans]
[Julio] You arrogant prick!
It was so easy to find you!
All I needed to do was offer a reward!
-That easy, huh?
-[Julio] Yes!
I didn't want to do this here.
But because I've had it with you,
I will kill you right here.
I will hang you in this exact place.
I will let your body rot,
and then I will feed you to the dogs!
But before I do all that… Get him up!
-Come on. Get up!
-[Julio] Hurry!
[Julio] Before I do all that,
I will kill you now.
I'll kill you, first!
[Jose] Congressman, cover!
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
[bystanders screaming]
-Jepoy!
-[Jepoy] Run!
[Anna] Jepoy!
[gunshots]
[Jepoy] Run!
[tires screeching]
-Jepoy, get in!
-[Julio] Jaguar!
[gunfire continues]
[Julio] Jaguar!
[gunfire]
[tense music swelling]
[screams in frustration]
Stupid!
[tense music playing]
I'm glad we finally have
a witness against Emilia.
-Auntie.
-Oh, thank you, Diego.
[Loring] And that's not
the only good news.
The doctor says your health is improving.
So, after a little more rest,
you can be discharged.
[chuckling]
[soft music playing]
Diego.
Where's Lily?
I guess it's good she isn't
visiting. It's too dangerous.
[Loring] Please. Eat up.
-So you can leave sooner.
-I'll eat later.
-Oh, hello.
-Mom.
Dear.
Mr. Pandoy.
Lily.
[soft music continues]
Have you eaten, Mom?
Not yet. Join me.
[Ivy and Camia giggling]
Miss Loring, Mr. Pandoy,
thank you for taking care of my mother.
-Don't mention it.
-There's no need to thank us.
-Ivy.
-Ivy, eat.
-Have some noodles.
-Please, keep eating.
Thank you.
Mom.
[Ivy] Come on. Eat.
-Okay.
-[Diego] Dessert?
[sinister music playing]
Boss, thank you for saving me back there.
I owe you my life.
Well, then. How about you pay us back?
Join our operation.
[tense music playing]
You know, I'm just wondering, Aunt Claire…
How did Raul find out
that Jaguar has an impostor?
Only Jaguar knew that he had an impostor.
How could he know that? And before,
it was just okay for Raul
that Jaguar was pursuing me.
And now, all of a sudden, he's so mad.
I don't understand it anymore.
Come on, Emilia.
Just don't bother with
Jaguar One, Jaguar Two,
and especially not Raul
because it will only complicate
all of your problems.
[sighs] I guess you're right.
Mrs. Emilia.
Wow, finally. Any good news?
Madam.
A CCTV camera recorded
Divine Uytengco being kidnapped.
Two men blew the tires
off the bodyguard's cars
so they couldn't follow.
Let me see that.
[ominous music playing]
Huh?
I'm sure Divine isn't the only one
who wants to testify
against the Ardientes.
There are plenty more out there,
victims of the Ardientes.
They want to testify,
but they're scared of getting killed.
That's why every move we make
has to be in secret.
It'll take the Ardientes by surprise.
They won't have time to sabotage us.
We know the Ardientes.
What's important is we have Divine.
Somebody will testify for us.
Mom, that's because of you.
That's because of
your investigation into Emilia.
This is the result of that.
Thank you, Mom.
[somber music playing]
Mom.
Lily… I can't help but be emotional.
If Raul didn't take me and make me weak…
I would have been with you
again much earlier.
All of this would have been over long ago.
Mom, we're here now.
What's important is we're together again.
It's the two of us.
We're taking down the next
Ardiente on our list.
Diego will fight Julio.
And he will win the election.
We will win, Mom.
Lily, I'm so proud of you.
And I'm sure if your father were here,
he'd be proud of you too.
This is all for Dad, Mom.
It's for our family.
[somber music continues playing]
Boss, aren't we going in yet?
It looks like Jaguar's men aren't coming.
The shipment would be wasted
if we let it go.
There's a saying, "The early bird
catches the worm."
But, more importantly, that bird
is beaten by bad timing.
Count down.
Five! Four! Three! Two! One!
Very good! Let's go!
[action music playing]
[man] This is it, boss.
[man] Okay, be careful.
-Boss, somebody's coming!
-Hurry up!
[man] Cover us.
Are you ready? Let's go.
One, two…
Let's go!
[gunshots]
[Jepoy] Leave no one alive!
Where's the driver?
Do you want to live? Come with us.
[action music playing]
Get in the cars. Close the truck.
[singing] La, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la…
La, la, la, la, la!
Lily!
Anna, what happened to you?
It's Jepoy.
What happened to Jepoy?
[tense music playing]
[action music playing]
All right, bring the goods out.
[tense music playing]
[Damian makes taunting noise]
[Damian laughs]
You're dead!
[gunshots]
Hey, fake Jaguar! The original's back!
Can you tell me how you fit
that big head of yours inside my mask?
You'd better give it back!
[Raul] You won't get it back!
I'm the only Jaguar here!
You?
[laughing]
Funny, 'cause when I came back,
your men sided with their true master!
Just admit it! You're a little house cat
pretending to be a ferocious jaguar!
[gunfire]
[action music playing]
[both grunting]
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[Damian] I won't let you off that easy!
I'll show you just
what a real Jaguar can do!
[tense music playing]
[both grunting]
[grunting]
[action music continues playing]
[gunshot]
-[screaming]
-[gunshot]
-[Jepoy] Hey!
-[gunshots]
[tense music playing]
[Raul] Madrigal!
Boss!
[tense music playing]
What's wrong, boss?!
If not for you, the operation
would have succeeded!
-You did this on purpose, didn't you?!
-No, boss! Why would I do that?!
Quit acting so innocent.
Boss, forgive me
for whatever it is I've done.
I didn't mean to.
I didn't do anything wrong.
[suspenseful music]
Boss, please.
I'll be honest with you.
Yes, I saved you from Julio
so you could help us with this operation.
But, after that,
I was planning to kill you.
Boss.
Because your fate has been decided.
[tense music playing]
Is this really Jaguar's hideout?
Yes, it's here.
I had them followed
after we met at the restaurant.
[action music playing]
Boss, what did I ever do to you?
I've been on your side since the start!
I'm your most loyal man!
To me? Nothing. But to my son? A lot.
Say your prayers.
[tense music playing]
[explosion]
-[Diego] Ivy. Ivy, let's go.
-Jepoy.
[Raul coughing]
[men coughing]
Madrigal!
[man coughing]
[tense music playing]
[Anna crying]
Jepoy! Jepoy!
I hope he got out of there alive!
Diego, we need to help Jepoy!
We need to find him!
[Anna sobbing]
Anna, calm down.
Diego.
Nothing bad's going to happen to him.
Anna, listen here…
As long as we haven't found Jepoy's body,
there's nothing to worry about, okay?
We know what Jepoy's capable of.
He can handle himself.
Jepoy was already there with me.
But I couldn't do anything to help him!
Diego, this is my fault!
Anna, this isn't your fault.
We will save Jepoy, okay?
We will find him!
Diego…
[Anna sobbing]
[tense music playing]
[sensual music playing]
[wincing]
[groaning]
[Jepoy] Boss, what did I ever do to you?
[Raul] To me? Nothing. But to my son?
Say your prayers.
[explosion]
[grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
[soft music playing]
Fine. I'll do what you want.
I'll keep my distance.
Just make sure you keep your word.
So, are we good?
[explosion]
-[Diego] Ivy. Ivy, let's go.
-Jepoy.
[soft music playing]
Ivy.
Anna's fine now.
[soft music continues playing]
I'm just worried about Jepoy.
I hope he's all right.
I hope he's alive somewhere.
Why did this have to happen now
when our plans were going so well?
Ivy, we won't give up.
We'll keep fighting.
Stay strong.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
It's Jepoy.
Jepoy?
-Ivy.
-Jepoy, where are you?
Jepoy, where are you?
I want you to come home.
And I don't want you
to ever leave again. Understand?
Jepoy, come home.
Ivy… I don't know where I am.
I'll call you later.
Jepoy.
What did he say?
It was Jepoy, but I don't know
where he is. He didn't either.
But, at least, he's safe.
I hope he's in good hands.
[tense music playing]
What matters is that he's alive.
[tense music intensifies]
[door opening]
[tense music playing]
Surprised?
You? Ma'am.
Um, you can say, "Thank you."
Thank you.
[chuckles] You sound so disappointed.
Aren't you happy to see me?
I thought you liked me.
[tense music playing]
I have to go, ma'am.
Not so fast, big boy.
[grunts]
Jaguar may have saved you.
But he just used you for the operation.
And he almost killed you.
If not for me.
So, will you still go back to Jaguar?
What do you want?
Wait.
Don't you like it?
What do you really want?
Why did you save me from Jaguar?
Ma'am, I'll only return a favor once.
So, tell me. What is it that you want?
[tense music playing]
Fine.
I want you to work for me.
Let's take Jaguar down.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
Sleep well, Arnaldo.
And don't ever wake up.
I'll be right here.
To keep my friends close,
and my enemies closer.
[Emilia] Have me investigated?
I don't know why you're still alive!
I won't let someone like you
put me behind bars!
Do you understand?!
[Ivy] You used your wealth
to intimidate others.
But you can't buy justice, Emilia.
Run as far as your legs can carry you.
Now it's time for you to face
the consequences of your crimes.
You cannot do this to me!
[theme music playing]